我们 是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
残品
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
presisco
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
拉尔斯, 你还好吗?
Lars, are you okay?
幸亏有你的泡泡...
Thanks to your bubble...
我的骨头只断了一点点
my bones are only a little broken.
我的也是
My bones, too.
伙计, 那些女巨人对你生了那么大气
Dude, those giant ladies were furious with you.
她们是钻石
They're the diamonds.
她们已经盯上我妈6000年了,
They've been after my mom for 6,000 years,
而现在她们又盯上了我
and now they're after me.
快点, 我们得走了
Come on. We got to move.
我们该怎么离开这个星球?
How are we supposed to get off this planet?
你真的知道你在往哪走吗?
Do you even know where you're going?
不, 我也是第一次来这里
No. This is my first time here, too.
这真是糟透了
This is so messed up.
我们能吃什么?
What are we gonna eat?
如果你喜欢吃石头的话 石头有的是
There's tons of food if you like rocks for dinner.
盐也算一种石头, 对吧?
Salt is a rock, right?
或许往土上撒点盐也能当饭吃
Maybe we can season some dirt and make a meal.
等下!
Wait!
呃...
Uh...
抱歉
Sorry.
他们发现我们了!
They found us!
-快跑! -等等!
-Run! -Wait!
如果我们静止不动的话, 它就看不到我们!
If we stand perfectly still, it won't see us!
我在电影里看到过
I saw it in a movie once.
听起来不错
That sounds good.
呃...我们得躲开了!
Uh... We should probably move!
啊!
Aah!
我想那部电影是关于恐龙的
I think that movie was about dinosaurs.
拉尔斯, 快!
Lars, come on!
喔!
Whoa!
我们该怎么做? 会发生什么?
What are we gonna do? What's gonna happen?
我们得逃跑 我们会没事的!
We're gonna run, and we're gonna be okay!
不!
No!
你没理解我的意思!
You just don't get it!
我讨厌一味躲避!
I hate being scared all the time!
我害怕所有事, 除了烘焙
I was scared of everything except baking.
实际上, 我也害怕那个
Actually, I was scared of that, too.
我甚至都不敢尝试做果仁蜜饼, 因为看起来太难了!
I never even tried making baklava 'cause it looked so hard!
我从没有胆量保护任何人...
I never had the guts to stick up for anybody...
甚至我自己!
not even me!
而现在我像个怂逼大屌丝似的躲在一个太空建筑下面!
And now I'm hiding again like a big cowardly loser under some space building!
不要这样打击自己, 拉尔斯
Don't beat yourself up like that, Lars.
打击是那些杀人机器的工作
That's what the killer robots are for.
-快! -下面!
-Quickly! -Down here!
史蒂文! 万一这是个陷阱呢?
Steven! What if it's a trap?
呃...我不认为我们有的选!
Uh... I don't think we have a choice!
啊!
Aah!
真险啊, 对吧?
Close one, huh?
没错, 但谁--
Yeah, but who --
别担心
Don't worry.
你们现在安全了
You're safe now.
我们不会伤害你
We're not gonna hurt you.
谢谢, 不论你们是...
Thank you, whoever you...
没事, 拉尔斯
It's okay, Lars.
谢谢你救了我们
Thank you for saving us.
真是怪了 他们是什么?
How bizarre. What are they?
但可以肯定他们和我们见过的宝石人不一样
They certainly don't look like gems we've ever seen before.
快, 这里!
Come, this way!
这里, 快!
This way, come!
史蒂文, 等等-这真是个好主意吗?
Steven, wait. - Is this really a good idea?
她们看起来...不一样, 我觉得我们可以信任她们
They seem...different. I think we can trust them.
呃, 不好意思, 但, 呃, 你要带我们去哪里?
Uh, excuse me, but, um, where are you taking us?
某个早已被遗忘的地方
Somewhere long forgotten.
属于无处可归者的归所
Where only those who don't belong belong.
听起来像是我这种人的去处
- Sounds like my kind of place.
这里不会碰巧
You don't happen to have
有卖快餐的小店吧?
any fast-food joints around there, do you?
喔!
Whoa!
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
宝宝基地
A kindergarten.
超超超大的那种
A really, really big one.
我们回来了!
We're back!
我们来了!
Here we are!
可以出来了!
It's okay to come out!
哦, 感谢老天, 我希望你们没被跟踪
Oh, thank goodness. I hope you weren't followed.
你们没被跟踪吧? 你确定吗?
You weren't, right? You double-checked?
你们被跟踪了!
You've been followed!
呃, 嗨!
Uh, hi!
呃, 别担心-我没有危险的
Uh, don't worry. - I'm not a threat or anything.
没事的, 蔷薇辉石
It's okay, Rhodonite.
放松, 我们带他们来这里的
Relax. We brought them here.
他们和我们是一伙的
They're with us.
我们能信任他们吗?
Can we trust them?
-当然-我觉得可以
-Sure. -I think so.
-大家好! -呃?
-Everyone! -Huh?
一个奇异的幻像出现在了我眼前
A wondrous vision has appeared before me.
金红石双胞胎会带回一个--不, 两个--
The twins of rutile will bring one -- no, two --
陌生人到我们目前的躲藏处
strangers to our current place of hiding.
我们知道的, 帕德玛蓝宝石
We know, Padparadscha.
你的预言已经发生了
Your prediction already happened.
他们在地表被那些
They were being chased up on the surface
恐怖的机器追赶着
by one of those terrible robonoids.
别告诉我你们试图与那种东西战斗
Don't tell me you tried to fight those things.
不, 不, 当然不
No, no. Of course not.
我们把他俩拉到地下之前
These two were about to be scanned
他俩险些就被扫描到了
when we pulled them under.
时机刚刚好
We were just in time.
让我看看
Let me see.
呃...
Uh...
啊!
Aah!
他们看起来不像是宝石人
They don't look like gems.
我就是这么说的!
That's what I said!
我也是这么说的!
I said the same thing!
嗨! 我是史蒂文, 我是个宝石人
Hi! I'm Steven. I'm a gem.
呃, 半个宝石人
Well, half-gem.
这是拉尔斯, 他是个人类
And this is Lars. He's all human.
难怪你们看起来如此不同寻常
That's why you look so unusual.
"我们"看起来不同寻常?!
We look unusual?!
当然!
Of course you do!
你不能就这么在地表乱逛!
You can't just walk around on the surface like that!
你是个残品--就像我们其余所有人!
You're off-color -- just like the rest of us!
残品是什么意思?
What do you mean, off-color?
你懂的, 错误的
You know, wrong.
不正确的
Not, right.
有瑕疵的
Flawed.
等等, 我没看出你们有任何问题啊
Wait, I don't see anything wrong with you guys.
像我们这样的宝石人是无用的
Gems like us aren't needed.
帕德玛只能预言刚刚发生过的事情
Padparadscha can only predict things that just happened.
萤石来了!
Here comes Fluorite!
而像我这样的融合体是不可原谅的
And a fusion like me is unforgivable.
当我的--我们的摩根石发现之后,
When my -- our Morganite found out,
这么说吧-我们被替换了
let's just say we were replaced.
但我们的故事可不算什么!
But my story's nothing!
我是指, 萤石, 你现在是多少个宝石人了?
I mean, Fluorite, - how many gems are you now?
六个
Six.
也许会更多, 如果我们遇到合适的宝石人的话
Maybe more, if we meet the right gem.
还有我们!
And then there's us!
你是说, 你不是个融合体?
You mean, you're not a fusion?
我们只是一个出错的金红石
We're just a rutile that came out wrong.
我们幸存了下来-因为其他所有的金红石
We survived - because all the other rutiles
在我们出生时都被吓跑了
ran away when we emerged.
我们幸存了下来, 因为她们害怕我们
We survived because they were afraid of us.
害怕你们?
Afraid of you?
所以你们一生都在躲避
So you've been hiding your whole lives.
如果它们发现了你们会怎么样?
What happens if they find you?
我们会被...
We'll be...
粉碎
Shattered.
-哦 -不!
-Oh. -No!
哦
Oh.
啊! 你们就是被跟踪了! 他们要发现我们了!
Ah! You were followed! They're gonna find us!
他们会将我们分开的!
They're gonna break us!
这是我们的错!
This is our fault!
如果不是因为我们, 你们也不会出事的!
If it wasn't for us, you'd be fine!
我们不能抛弃你们不管啊
We couldn't just leave you there.
我们得做点什么
We had to do something.
史蒂文? 我们该怎么办?
Steven? What're we gonna do?
所有人躲起来!
Everyone hide!
小心, 所有人! 我们要被发现了!
Careful, everyone! We're about to be found!
拉尔斯...
Lars...
害怕是没关系的
It's okay to be afraid.
好吧
Okay.
哦, 不!
Oh, no!
我们得做点什么!
We got to do something!
拉尔斯!
Lars!
拉尔斯
害怕是没关系的
It's okay to be afraid.
哦, 我的天! 拉尔斯!
Oh, my gosh! Lars!
它们是要扫描你的宝石!
They were trying to scan your gem!
它们根本看不见你!
They can't see you at all!
好吧!
All right!
看来要翻盘了!
Looks like the tables have turned!
-人类拉尔斯
-Human Lars.
一个最非凡的幻像-占据了我的脑海!
I've been possessed - by the most marvelous vision!
啊?
Huh?
你, 人类拉尔斯, 没有宝石
You, human Lars, are gemless,
因而不会被那些机器伤害到
and will be safe from the robonoids,
因为它们只瞄准宝石!
which only target gems!
这是我这辈子做过的最酷的事了
I think that's the coolest thing I've ever done in my life.
还没结束呢
It's not over yet.
哈?
Huh?
哦-护盾有反射功能
Oh. - The shield is reflective.
帕德玛, 快回来! 躲起来!
Padparadscha, come back! Hide!
好吧
Okay.
好吧!
Okay!
尝尝这个!
Eat this!
拉尔斯!
Lars!
拉尔斯?
Lars?
我以为我们做不到的!
I didn't think we were gonna make it!
-那真是太妙了! -拉尔斯, 你太棒了
-That was amazing! -Lars, that was so great.
-你太伟大了-我们快赢了!
-You were amazing. -We're winning!
我们要赢了!
We're winning!
喔
Whoa.
发生了什么?
What happened?
哦, 我的天!
Oh, my!
拉尔斯身上就要发生神奇的事了!
Something incredible is going to happen to Lars!